manaflask.com 2012-11-30

# Top Raiding: Guides, Streams, Interviews and Blogs

This policy is effective as of April 14, 2009.

At Manaflask.com (the "Site") we care strongly about your right to privacy and therefore we have several privacy settings on our Site that limits people's access to your information. However you are always in control of your own information since you decide when and what to enter and share with the community or your friends.

## Information Gathering, Using and Cookies

We as most other web sites run tools that might be invisible to the user, these tools automatically collects information from our visitors, for example a Cookie which helps us identify you when you revisit the site, or identify your browser to help us make sure the site displays correctly for you. We also for example log the name of your Internet Service Provider and IP-address. The information we gather is used to enhance your user experience on the website and other services and to deliver more individualized content and advertising. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information obtained at Manaflask.com or Services for other purposes, including but not limited to administration of the site, contests, sweep takes, support, sending newsletters. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our website, for example our web hosting service, may possibly access such information if needed. We may also use some of your information that does not indentify you as an individual with third parties, for example if a lot of people have the same sort of favorites we could possibly try and tailor some personalized content towards this group via a third party. We will use your information only as permitted by law. will use your information only as permitted by law.

## Removing or Changing Information

Most personal information on Manaflask is available through the account settings, users may delete or modify any of their account/profile settings at any time by utilizing their account

## Third Parties

Some third parties namely advertisement on Manaflask.com might send you a cookie, this Privacy Policy only covers the use of Cookies by Manaflask and does not cover the use of cookies or any other tracking technologies by any of our advertisers.

Manaflask contain links to other websites and third party content, we are not responsible for the privacy practice of such content or sites. We strongly encourage our users to read the privacy statement on those sites before using or accessing the content.

## Children

Manaflask does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information about or from children under the age of 13 except as permitted by law. If we find any information from a child under 13 on the Site we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Manaflask.com has any information about or from anyone under the age of 13 please contact us.

We also recommend that any children between the age of 13 and 18 ask their parents or legal guardians for permission before submitting any personal information to Manaflask.com.

## Security

Manaflask takes a lot of precautions to protect our users’ information. Your information is for example located and stored within Europe’s most secure data center, also known as "The Bunker", an ultra secure underground Military Grade facility, protected by both integrated processes for physical, digital and human security.
